The Titans go ninja on the notorious villain Brushogun in
their awesome first feature-length movie.
Teen Titans: Trouble in Tokyo is a animation, action,
science fiction film directed by Michael Chang.
After a battle with a high-tech villain named, Saiko-Tek, the Teen Titans travel to the city of
Tokyo where they find themselves embroiled in a conflict with an ancient enemy.
Beast Boy (voice), played by Greg Cipes.
Robin / Japanese Boy (voice), played by Scott Menville.
Cyborg (voice), played by Khary Payton.
Raven / Computer (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Starfire / Mecha-Boi (voice), played by Hynden Walch.
Mayor / Bookseller (voice), played by Robert Ito.
Teen Titans: Trouble in Tokyo is a 2006 American made-for-TV animated superhero
film adaptation of the DC Comics superhero team Teen Titans.
Based on the animated series Teen Titans that ran on Cartoon Network
from 2003 to 2006, the film serves as the series finale.
It premiered on Cartoon Network, on September 15, 2006.
Teen Titans head writer David Slack wrote the film.
The film explores themes of villain, fraud, based
on comic, tokyo, japan, arrested.
The tone is thought_provoking.